ansh46.com 2014-10-07

# Privacy Policy | ANSH46 Designer Clothing Store

€1,295 

€759 

€845 

€845 

€47 

€47 

€1,025 

€415 

€655 

€1,575 

€345 

€655 

€225 

€545 

€156 

€465 

€759 

€759 

€655 

€324 

€495 

€165 

€765 

€254 

€189 

PRIVACY AND SECURITY

1. | [DATA PROTECTION](http://www.ansh46.com/privacy#18) | 5. | [ORDER PLACEMENT](http://www.ansh46.com/privacy#22)  
---|---|---|---  
2. | [SECURITY POLICY](http://www.ansh46.com/privacy#19) | 6. | [SEVERANCE](http://www.ansh46.com/privacy#23)  
3. | [PRIVACY POLICY](http://www.ansh46.com/privacy#20) | 7. | [PAYMENT OBLIGATION](http://www.ansh46.com/privacy#24)  
4. | [THIRD PARTY RIGHTS](http://www.ansh46.com/privacy#21) |   |    
  
By submitting an order you agree to the processing by us of your personal information and the disclosure of that information as set out in this clause 8. Further information about the manner in which we process your information is set out in our privacy policy.

We may use any personal information provided to us by you or obtained by us from any third party relating to you for any purposes relating to the provision of our goods and services.

You agree that we may use Personal information provided by you in order to conduct appropriate anti fraud checks. Personal Information that you provide may be disclosed to a credit reference or fraud prevention agency, which may keep a record of that information.

We may notify you by e-mail or by post about goods and services available from ANSH46. If you would prefer not to receive such information please e-mail us at the following address: customerservice@ANSH46.com

We may disclose any personal information provided to us by you or obtained by us from any third party relating to you to:

Any person, firm or company to whom we may sell the whole or a substantial part of our business or to whom we may transfer any part of our rights or obligations under this agreement; and For the purposes of assisting us in providing our goods and services and maintaining and supporting any equipment utilised by us we may need to disclose or provide access to personal data held by us relating to you to the supplier of such equipment or any third party providing maintenance and support services. Any such disclosure or access will be made under strict terms of confidentiality. Any such disclosure or transfer referred to above may take place via electronic means using the internet (or otherwise).

The disclosures which we may make under clauses 8.4 and 8.5 above may involve the transfer of personal data relating to you to countries outside the european economic area which countries may not have in place adequate rules relating to data protection and privacy of personal data.

We use secure socket layer technology (ssl). This means that when you place orders with us on our secure online ordering system, all of the information is encrypted or scrambled, so that the data you send is an unintelligible string of seemingly random characters. When these characters are received by our web server, the server's ssl software converts them back into useful information. The same thing happens with data you receive from our server. Your interactions are therefore private.

## PROTECTING YOUR SECURITY

To ensure that your credit, debit or charge card is not being used without your consent, we will validate name, address and other personal information supplied by you during the order process against appropriate third party databases. By accepting these terms and conditions you consent to such checks being made. In performing these checks personal information provided by you may be disclosed to a registered Credit Reference Agency which may keep a record of that information. You can rest assured that this is done only to confirm your identity, that a credit check is not performed and that your credit rating will be unaffected. All information provided by you will be treated securely and strictly in accordance with the Data Protection Act 1998.

You agree that we may use Personal information provided by you in order to conduct appropriate anti fraud checks. Personal Information that you provide may be disclosed to a credit reference or fraud prevention agency, which may keep a record of that information.

We will validate name, address and other personal information supplied by you during the order process against appropriate third party databases. By accepting these terms and conditions you consent to such checks being made. In performing these checks personal information provided by you may be disclosed to a registered Credit Reference Agency which may keep a record of that information. You can rest assured that this is done only to confirm your identity, that a credit check is not performed and that your credit rating will be unaffected. All information provided by you will be treated securely and strictly in accordance with the Data Protection Act 1998.

## HOW DOES IT WORK?

You only need to register with vBv and SecureCode once to create your password for each of your relevant payment cards. Then whenever you shop online using your registered cards you'll be asked to enter the relevant password as an additional validation before the order is confirmed. Simply follow the instructions that appear once you have submitted your order. The details you enter in this process will be submitted to your card issuer over a secure link and can not be viewed nor will they be held by ANSH46.

## WHAT IF I AM ALREADY REGISTERED?

If you've already registered you just need to enter your own personal password as indicated on the box that appears once you've submitted your order.

We take the security and privacy of our customers seriously and this policy sets out how we handle information about you and your rights in respect of that information.

What information do we hold and how do we obtain it? Generally we receive information directly from you when you place an order with us to buy our goods. Such information includes your name, address, email address, telephone number and credit card details.

For what purposes do we use your information? We use your information for a number of purposes including: - to perform our contractual obligations to you and to ensure that goods are supplied to you as efficiently as possible - for other non-contractual reasons.

We, or reputable third parties acting on our behalf, may use your information:

## TO IDENTIFY AND MAINTAIN RECORDS OF YOUR PURCHASES WITH US

To ensure that the goods and services we offer to you are appropriate for your needs, To respond to any query you may raise with us about our goods, To update our systems for providing you with an enhanced service, For our customers' protection, we always check a certain percentage of our orders at random to confirm the details of the order match those of the cardholder on file. For this reason, we may ask you for some additional information. This would be a copy of the front and back of the card used to make the purchase, or a copy of a photo ID such as a valid drivers license or passport. We will also require some proof of address along with the copy of the photo ID.

## OTHER PURPOSES

We will also use information about you for purposes upon which the provision of our goods and services are not necessarily dependent. We may:

disclose information about you to third party agencies for credit checking purposes (which information may be shared with other organizations for the same purpose) use information about you to inform you (by post email or telephone) about other services we offer or which are offered by other companies within our group or any of the other companies with which we work use information about your account with us for our internal customer service monitoring and training purposes

## TRANSFERS OVERSEAS

Please note that disclosures we may make may take place via electronic means and may involve the transfer of personal data relating to you to countries outside the european economic area which countries do not have in place adequate rules relating to data protection and privacy of personal data.

## SALE OF OUR BUSINESS

You acknowledge that data you provide to us may be transferred to any person, firm or company to whom we sell the whole or a substantial part of our business or to whom we transfer any of our rights or obligations under a contract with you.

## TAKING CARE OF YOUR DATA

We will endeavor to keep any information which we hold about you up to date and accurate. To help us to do this, please keep us informed if any of your details change. We will endeavor to protect your data against unauthorized or unlawful use. We use secure socket layer technology (ssl). This means that when you place orders with us on our secure online ordering system, all of the information is encrypted or scrambled, so that the data you send is an unintelligible string of seemingly random characters. When these characters are received by our web server, the server's ssl software converts them back into useful information. The same thing happens with data you receive from our server. Your interactions are therefore private.

The statutory right of any person other than you or us to enforce any of these provisions is excluded.

While browsing the website, items can be added to the shopping basket by choosing a size followed by clicking the button "add to basket ". You can either continue shopping or go to the checkout. The checkout pages will guide you through the rest of buying process. You will be able to delete items from the cart or make a change the quantity at any time.

If any term shall in whole or in part be held to any extent to be illegal or unenforceable under any enactment or rule of law that term shall to that extent be deemed not to form part of these terms and the enforceability of the remainder of the terms shall not be affected.

When you fail to meet the payment obligation, ANSH46 is not only entitled to demand the legal rate of interest over the owed sum, but also to all reasonable costs ANSH46 makes to acquire the chargeable sum. This forced payment is set at at least 15 % of the prior sum; if ANSH46 can show that it has made bigger costs, than these will also be taken in consideration for compensation.

CUSTOMER SERVICES  
T : +31 (0) 10 233 91 82  
E : info@ansh46.com
